you know tell me Edmond was coming to
dinner with Grandma
is it great your cousin in town from San
Francisco actually it's Palo Alto that's
where
most of the tech industry is now yeah
sure sure yeah I only go to San
Francisco to
get my Tesla serve us yeah more like his
testy service
you know Nora here's uh moving out she's
starting her own career
oh yeah how's that going it's going
super dope super dope super dope uh got
temporarily fired from commutes what
what is this commutes live I'm gonna eat
her ass
beat her ass yeah hey maybe uh Edmund
can get you a job
huh what do you say bro
uh well Uncle Wally it's kind of hard to
get a job in Tech pretty much to my
colleagues went to Ivy League schools
most have advanced degrees and
Nora has this certificate from my TT
talk oh she loves computers maybe she
works for Apple Store yeah more like the
Microsoft store
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay Tokyo Drift
of all the Rideshare drivers in New York
do you want a water
yeah do a charger actually
hot argument joking with this hair right
now no are you taking a picture it's the
exact color and consistency of Johnny
Depp's reprisal of the Mad Hatter on him
weak what are you doing in New York I
live here now what I left Palo Alto I'm
going solo like Kelly Rowland
hello doing what
why not
while your parents happy at least that
you're back they don't know I'm here and
don't tell them okay why not just stop
asking questions okay
donations you took a commutes to go 500
feet I'm wearing ferragamos and there is
urine all over this city and you're
living here Edmond a studio in this
apartment costs like ten thousand
dollars a month imagine when I'm paying
for the penthouse the White House
goodbye Nora
foreign
[Music]
follow me on Instagram
holy what
so
Uncle penis Uncle penis is a dad penis
why would you show it to me you must
have accidentally posted it and just
didn't see the mirror behind him oh it
has like 200 likes which proportionately
doesn't make sense because he has 17
followers we need to delete that thing
he's gonna become a meme even if he
deletes it off his personal account
other people have screenshotted it no no
we need we need to get the original off
we need to get the screenshots off I
need duplicates we just scrubbed the
internet off that picture that needs to
go oh that means to go
you are an idiot but also with God damn
genius okay I gotta go I gotta go um I
gotta go where are you going to go and
code scrubber it shouldn't take long I
just have to match a proprietary data
set to an image labeling model and then
it'll be
you're leaving yeah and you won't be
back for a while yeah bye can I can I
ask you one more thing what
did you just feel anything ew no just
disgusting I didn't either I didn't
either
I've been coding all night and I finally
finished the beta and I think this app
could be huge oh wow I'm so proud of you
Edmond well the harder part is thinking
of the app which I did in 3.5 seconds
and counting oh so I'm proud of you too
Nora yeah I literally invented an entire
server okay so yeah well Grandma loves
you more so I hope you're all right with
that okay just Nora you don't know what
it's about to happen okay if this app
gets up and running we are looking at
potentially raking in millions we need
to get my dad's dick off the internet
before Jerry finds it and okay just
it's fine whatever can I just run my app
presentation for you guys because I just
need to practice before the investor
meeting tomorrow and no of course red
leather yellow leather red leather
yellow leather the dragon will come when
he hears the drum and to minute her two
till two
y'all ready for this
scrubber is an app that can change the
world by using micro patterns compiled
from each binary based representation of
a pixel or local binary pattern or a
patented LBP we can run the image
through our neural network and this
outputs a set of measurements that serve
as a unique
identifier
said nudes more like unsend nudes
I'm just gonna start over and
um oh okay so leg cramp leg cramp oh my
God I'm burning up it's like
I'm on the beach in Mykonos
God you're sweating very profusely right
now just smell that it smells like
turmeric what is wrong with him
I don't know okay
oh
I'll leave you with this we're all born
the same way
naked and screaming thank you so much
that's good right had a good flow had a
good structure yeah
yeah no notes
I'm not good
oh
[Music]
okay all right okay I'm sorry let me get
this straight
you got fired because of what
a court summons
oh is this yes my mother has been
indicted in the College admission
Scandal for extortion and bribery what I
got into Stanford solely because she
bribed the fencing coach into admitting
me on an athletic scholarship for what
sport fencing I said oh and it was
actually passionate and good at it for
11 years okay but you still went to
Stanford right you still got a Stanford
education nor I could never show my face
in Silicon Valley I get my life is
meaningless
ah
are you smiling right now no this is not
a smile I'm just airing my teeth out
it's just that I've always been a little
jealous of you not jealous of the tale
which you know I have gripped I did I
have done one of those but then you
became such an accomplished awesome
person and now seeing just how you
are and everything is for you
it's comforting I'm glad that my demise
and Anatomy bring you inner peace Nora
yeah
my mind went to some Dark Places I
thought about all the and all
the posturing like nothing I did in Tech
actually benefited Humanity yeah I mean
maybe this is my wake-up call Maybe This
Is The Universe telling me admin to give
back to the world you took so much from
give back I know it will be hard but
it's what I have to do oh man that's so
beautiful I'm so proud of you what are
we talking about like non-profit work
charity work acting
oh it's a cure okay what are we doing
what even is a self tape it's like an
audition but you do it from home and
instead of doing one take you do like 26
and then after you're done you send in
your favorite one and then hello the CW
yeah but these rules are super intense
dude they want to shoot you horizontal
yeah what does that mean landscape mode
I don't think we should do it Nora a
monkey could do this
[Music]
man you're so on that side frame up that
way okay yep you ready because you need
to go left more I'm out you're totally
out yeah you're in what's my range of
motion that if you can't control that
bit
yeah
[Applause]
if you can't handle that no sorry I was
on Photo all right here we go
if you can't control that okay it looks
so bad on video now it's like a whole
different lens what do you mean
if you can't control that I will
if you can't handle the I will if
you can't control the I will if
you can't control that
if you can't control that
I felt that if you can't control that
I will cut on rehearsal that was so good
you weren't recorded no no I wasn't
recording those
okay please let your name
edlin five foot eight five foot nine in
the mornings I am reading for Jonathan
great ready when you are I'm ready
Connor oh man there you go smack talking
us again Chloe don't be afraid to take
home your second place trophy boys
didn't you leave them here last time
yeah
like in my ass
that was great Ed but this time can you
do that with a little less Crescendo on
the ah part of ass yes absolutely thanks
and action
that was a cloud that was
that was the weather the best piece of
the chicken this right here can't be the
right place
that's the right place you want some
chicken you know no okay
yeah it's hot
hey
hi is this for the audition yeah it's
for Jurassic Park
internally
you still in yeah yeah
I'll be right here I'm not moving I will
not leave your side
come over here hit your mark
okay so there's uh something in front of
you I think it's an egg you're gonna
pick it up
you're gonna kiss it and then roll it
off stage left
oh another there's a little limosource
Rex standing directly in front of you
you approach it in Wonder pick it up
hold it hold it hold it now you're gonna
it
sorry excuse me
I mean you're gonna kiss it on the cheek
oh sorry
oh my God I just got a call back you
still want to it
so I'm gonna go
it's like I'm living with present day
Randy Quaid
[Music]
oh
what is my
my life
Ryan Daddy he could get it what
Amanda why are you so goddamn noisy I'm
so sorry to wake you from your Slumber
but
I can't leave your room without catching
hep C
okay no Nora your room is
foul and if you don't clean your room
today I'm throwing all of your
outside and advertising it on a poll
correct me if I'm wrong but you living
under my roof you're what my roof why
are you saying roof like that also I'm
aware that you and Uncle Wally and
Grandma are housing me at the moment but
you can't make me feel bad about it
because you don't know what it's like to
be a struggling actor okay which is
because I'm not an actor doesn't mean
that I'm not struggling the whole City's
struggling Edmund
yeah okay I get that I'm sorry I think
I'm still adjusting to being canceled
and your personal hygiene and your
overall way of being it's honestly sad
messiness is a sign of intelligence and
in the 2000s girls can be both messy and
intelligent as well
[Music]
hot cut cut
what are you doing I'm dismembering him
I don't know something's off Let's Lose
the knife and try a gun bringing the gun
okay reset
in action
[Music]
[Applause]
this scene is garbage sorry Ed it's not
you but it is you because you're a part
of it but it's just not working it's
okay let's take five
Hey kid
I know this all sucks I hate it here
it's a
truth is unless you working full time
for a Law and Order New York sucks for
film and TV if I didn't share custody
with my ex or my dumb ass kid I wouldn't
live here
you got to go to where the jobs flow
like a river after a storm
where everybody's happy and the weather
never changes
where the blow is as pure as the fresh
Colorado snow
[Music]
you feel me
where is this glorious place
is heaven
[Music]
like heaven
Nora Nora what you know how we always
say that New York isn't all that we
don't always say that yeah well okay if
I'm Gonna Be Acting I need to go where
the jobs flow like a river after a storm
where everyone is happy and the weather
never changes and the blow is as pure as
the fresh Colorado snow do you feel me
Reno Nevada baby no not really knowing
about it no it's the next best thing
anyway
Los Angeles
Hollywood it's been in front of me this
whole time
oh yeah for sure dude La uh if you can
make it in that City you can make it
anywhere
that's in New York yeah well you could
get make a brand new start of it no no
no no no I've made up my mind La here I
come
foreign